KanaKana Channel Go! Go!
Today's topic is my own yearbook clear
version.
Please.
The viewers are Momoka, Minami and Toa.
I chose these three from me.
Thank you.
The reason is that there are seven other
members other than me.
I chose the best three that I'm not
interested in.
I'm not interested in you.
How much do you know about me?
I don't know.
I know a lot about you.
I'll introduce you to a lot of people.
I was born on August 19, 2003.
I have a dog.
When I was born,
I had one dog.
I know.
The name of the dog I bought for the
first time is Gucci.
I don't remember until I was five years
old.
I was born when I was two years old.
I have two sisters.
When I was three years old,
I had two more sisters at the same time.
I got three sisters.
Do you know who I am?
Are you a girl?
It's a woman.
I'm a woman.
There is one more.
It's correct.
I don't know.
I'm Kenzo.
That's wrong.
I haven't heard of Kenzo yet.
I'm Romane.
I bought three sisters here.
I started learning to dance when I was
five years old.
That's early.
Is it early?
Well, well, well.
The reason I started learning at the age
of 5 was because my friend invited me to
a local dance school.
But I quit that friend about 6 months
ago.
Even though you were in the dance
school?
Yes.
But I've been dancing from the age of 5
to now.
I think I was 4 when I was 6 years old.
I was 7 or so.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here.
I don't know.
It's the same.
One more.
Yes.
I have one more.
Porsche.
Oh, it's close.
It's a car.
Benz?
Oh, it's close.
Lexus.
It's almost Benz.
It's called Mercedes.
Mercedes Benz.
I have 4 of them.
When I was 8 years old, I went to the
next neighborhood.
Next to the next.
I met a girl like this.
I'm surprised, I don't know exactly when
I met her.
Because I think she's a girl.
Oh, I can't say it, but it doesn't mean
that her Zaku is cool that much, right?
Yes.
A girl in Dome.
I heard that in Dome, you're normally
close to women who are close to women.
It's dangerous, I'm sure maybe, like me.
Then, you must be doing that.
Yes, that's true.
I started learning three genres here.
I've been in this industry for almost
three years.
I started learning another language
here.
Do you know?
Other than dance?
Other than dance.
I've been doing this for two years.
Piano?
No.
Impression?
English.
Correct.
I learned English for two years here.
But I don't have any experience in this
industry.
I see.
I learned only other than dance.
I heard that.
Really?
I'll learn more here.
Do you want to do it?
Name?
Let's go.
I don't know the car.
Car?
But here...
So...
Maybe not here.
Maybe around here.
And?
My agency...
My agency is related to this.
It's a boy.
A boy?
Genesis.
Oh!
It's a boy named Jene who was taken from
Genesis.
Why do you know that?
And the fifth one.
I often think about it.
Amazing.
When I was 10 years old, I was in an
exclusive audition for EXPG.
And the teacher of the school I was
attending started teaching me in PG.
I heard that there was an audition
there.
I heard that.
I was in an exclusive audition for EXPG
every year.
I was 10 years old when I was told that
I couldn't take it.
I think I was in the fourth grade.
I can only take it from the fourth
grade.
I see.
I was in the exclusive audition from the
fourth grade.
I don't know now.
I took the audition.
I fell.
You fell.
I want to fall.
I fell.
I'm sad.
So I was still learning.
But I was still there for another year.
I moved to another school.
I moved to the next town.
I lived in a house near the school.
I moved to another school.
And I took another year.
And another year passed.
And they asked me if I could take the
audition again the next year.
I didn't want to take it.
I really hated taking auditions.
My mother said,
I'll try to do my best for another year.
I was so happy.
Then one year passed.
Then I took the audition.
I took the audition.
So I took the audition.
Then I joined the XPG.
I entered the XPG.
At 11 years old.
After elementary school?
Yes, I joined the XPG from elementary
school.
I started buying cats around this time.
After this time, you have a cat.
Yes, I have 6 cats.
I have a lot.
I had a cat in the park nearby.
So I got a cat.
What?
I had a cat.
I met you when I entered here.
You were like a princess.
I was like a princess.
Now I think you are a princess.
I was a special student at the same time
as you.
You were one year younger than me.
I knew you were a special student.
I was a special student at that time.
I went to the lesson and I was waiting
for you.
You entered the last class.
Good morning.
You were like a princess.
You were a princess.
I'm kidding.
You were in the same class.
You entered the class at that time.
You were like a princess.
You were a princess.
Yes.
When I was around 13 years old,
I joined EXPG laboratory.
I saw the kommtal
at that time.
I met watching momoko.
Momoko went to Osaka school too.
Someлыmer,
Anna suddenly joined the team.
Suddenly I joined the team.
I was the same as four of you.
There were other members too.
We met around here.
And then, a rap lesson started online.
Did you do rap?
All the girls who were in there were
doing it.
We were doing it remotely.
We, Miyazaki High School, were doing it
in Fukuoka High School.
Misaki also came out.
I've never talked to her, but she's
always in the picture during the lesson.
At this time, I recognized Misaki.
We met around the same age.
Then, the following year, I got a talk
with Maji Maji Piyo.
I started to study here.
I transferred to a junior high school in
Tokyo around the middle of the second
grade.
I was 14 years old.
I started filming a drama.
I debuted when I was 15 years old.
I was in the third grade.
I debuted in Maji Maji.
And I forgot to tell you about Towa.
She's forgotten.
Before this audition, Towa joined this
team.
It was a question of whether she would
join or not.
Three girls came to the audition.
One of them was Towa.
She was so thin and had a twintail.
And she was good at dancing.
That was my impression.
That's amazing.
She was wearing a twintail.
She also acted with me.
Really?
I was an additional member of Maji Maji
Piyo.
We were in the same situation.
The shooting started late.
I had to take acting lessons on the days
I couldn't go on a tour.
And I had to take Towa's lessons.
Really?
It was like a cafe setting.
It was like a customer coming in.
I can't believe it.
I had acting lessons with Towa.
You're also anuchs.
When I had extra services, I was milked
by Towa who often told me about it.
We always tell each other about it.
Worked at Minajika.
That's a toy workshop in Tokyo.
We had respects in Tokyo.
Bow lek.
We played in a another plant.
I had this one-person bath ready out of
myILL.
This was very good.
But the best thing about it was you
really had to make out with someone.
I decided to go to university.
I started living alone when I was in
university.
I moved from here to here.
I will tell you the details.
I have 8 dogs and cats.
That's a lot.
I have more cats.
I have more dogs.
That's all.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
How was it?
Do you have any similarities?
With myself?
Yes.
The world is different.
I was born in Miyazaki prefecture.
When I moved to Tokyo, I said goodbye to
my parents here.
I lived with my grandmother here.
I lived here until now.
That's sad.
I said goodbye to my grandmother when I
was 14.
That's sad.
I'm lonely.
I think my grandmother was lonely.
When I moved to Tokyo, my classmates
were very nice to me.
I was impressed.
You moved to Tokyo in the last year.
I moved halfway.
I was in the middle of my junior year.
I moved to the middle of my junior year.
The middle school in Miyazaki prefecture
is halfway.
The middle school in Tokyo is halfway.
Are we only continuing the覺得 to move to
another high school ?
I'm interviewing.
I realized it's out of my mind.
I switched 촉 surprised by University.
I wanted to communicate that I've been
moved here for at least two years and my
life has changed to the other way
around.
I've been aside.
Why?
Because I've arrived in elementary
school.
In chasing the illuminance, I moved here
at a young age.
I've moved here since the 1st-year
Алent-se student had a child for three
years.
Any Ern Ellis drawings without children.
I went to this school for 4 to 6 years.
I went to a middle school in Miyazaki
for half a year.
I went to a high school in Tokyo for
half a year.
I went to a high school in Tokyo for 3
years.
I went to the same high school as Taha.
I transferred to a university after 2
years.
You're going to be half of that.
That's why.
I'm going to be half of my life plan for
40 years.
That's scary.
I don't know.
I'm going to be 60 or 80.
What are you going to do when you get to
work at 36 or 37?
You'll be like, I'm having fun.
Are you okay?
You're talking so quietly.
I'm worried about my throat.
I'm having fun.
What if you have only 2 or 3 years left?
What if you want to live a little
longer?
Then I'll live.
That's the plan at this point.
But I'm going to be half of my life.
I'm going to be half of my life at 38.
That's what I'm going to be like until
I'm 20.
I'm looking forward to it.
There's still half of it.
Half of my life.
I don't know if the three of you had
fun.
It was fun.
I think the people who came to see me
came because they wanted to know.
But I'm a little...
I'm a little...
I'm a little硬-
It's getting flexible and I bring it
it's still ready.
That's fine.
These people who came to see me came to
see me in the interesting ways.
After reading all of that, it's just
like an animation.
But I think a lot of people think that's
great.
This is also the first